好 罗斯
Uh, okay, Ross.
我知道你进来没想到会看到这一慕 但是…
I realize that you didn't expect to walk in and see that, but, uh...
- 听我解释好吗？ - 我们什么都没做
- Let me explain, okay?      - We weren't doing anything!
瑞秋 他看到了
Rach, he just saw us.
嘘
Shh.
但是我们就只有这样 一个吻而已
Uh, but what you saw, that is the extent of it, okay? One kiss.
- 谎言 我们在巴贝多就吻过了   - 哥们儿 冷静点
- That's a lie! We also kissed in Barbados.      - Dude, chill!
好吧 我们在巴贝多也吻过
Okay, we also kissed in Barbados...
但是我们不是故意的 发生这件事的唯一原因…
...but we didn't plan it. The only reason that happened...
是因为我看见你吻了查莉
...was because I saw you kiss Charlie.
对 是你开始的 我真的得冷静下来
Yeah, you started it! I have got to chill.
或许我们应该在 事情发生之前跟你说
Look, we probably should have talked to you about this before it ever happened.
- 可是…   - 我们真的感到很抱歉 罗斯
- But...     - Oh, we feel so terrible about this, Ross.
对 可是它确实发生了
Yeah. But it did happen.
所以…
So...
罗斯？
Ross?
我们可以直接关上门吗？
Can we just close the door?
罗斯 你说话啊
Ross, say something.
什么都行
Anything.
所以说你们两个…
So you two are?
对
Yeah.
那你们有没有…
And have you had?
- 没有   - 没有
- No. No, no, no.     - No. No.
如果我没闯进来 你们会不会…
But if I hadn't walked in here, would you?
也许…不…
Probably... No. No.
罗斯 我们本来就不希望让你 以这种方式发现
Ross, this is not how we wanted you to find out about this.
你有权利抓狂
You have every right to go nuts.
我不会抓狂的 你有看到我在抓狂吗？
I'm not going nuts. Do you see me going nuts?
不 可是你知道我的意思
No, but you know what I mean.
嘿…
Hey, hey, hey.
如果你们两人开心
If you two are happy...
我也会为你们开心
...then I'm happy for you.
我没事
I'm fine.
- 真的？ - 当然
- Really?     - Absolutely.
我没事
I'm fine.
完全没事
Totally fine.
我不知道为什么 我的声音又大又尖
Heh. I don't know why it's coming out all loud and squeaky...
因为… 说真的
because, really...
我没事
...I'm fine.
不是说看到你们接吻
I'm not saying I wasn't a little surprised...
一点也不令人感到吃惊
...heh, to see you guys kissing.
我是说 一开始我是有点…
I mean, at first I was like:
但现在我已经有时间来消化它…
But now that I've had time to absorb it...
我很喜欢
Loving this.
- 罗斯   - 一切都是那么圆满
- Ross...     - It's all working out.
我和查莉 还有你们两个
Me and Charlie. And you two.
- 你知道我们该做什么吗？ - 冷静下来？
- You know what we should do?     - Calm ourselves?
不
No.
我们应该一起吃顿晚餐
We should all have dinner.
对 我们明天晚上就吃 我来掌厨
Yes, we'll do it tomorrow night. I'll cook!
你不觉得那样太奇怪了吗？
Wow. Uh, look, don't you think that would be a little weird?
怪？为什么？哪里怪了？
Weird? What? What's weird? Huh?
如果有人不喜欢墨西哥菜 才是唯一的一件怪事
The only thing weird would be if someone didn't like Mexican food...
因为我要做法士达面饼
...because I'm making fajitas!
我是喜欢吃法士达面饼
I do like fajitas.
天啊 领养小孩真是累死人了
God, this adoption stuff is so overwhelming.
跨国领养 从属领养…
There's inter-country adoption, dependency adoption.
有这么多方法 而这是我们一生最大的决定
There's so many ways to go, and this is, like, the biggest decision of our lives.
我咖啡里有头发
There's a hair in my coffee.
- 嘿 你们   - 嘿
- Hey, guys.     - Hey.
有看到小法兰克吗？他要带三胞胎来看我
Have you seen Frank Jr? He's meeting me here with the triplets.
太有意思了 每次你说"三胞胎"
It's funny, every time you say "triplets"...
我 马上就想到三个 火辣的十九岁金发女郎
...I think of three hot, blond 19-year-olds.
真可爱
Oh, that's sweet.
喝你的头发吧
Drink your hair.
这些是什么？
Hey, what's all this stuff?
这些是我们从不同的领养中心 拿来的小册子
Oh, they're brochures from different adoption agencies.
小孩子 这个好可爱
Ooh, babies! Oh, this one is so cute.
领养这个
Get this one.
程序完全不是这样运作的
That's not really how it works.
- 那怎么运作？ - 我不知道
- Oh, how does it work?     - I don't know!
如果你们遇到什么困难 应该找我的朋友谈谈
If you're having a hard time, you should talk to my friends...
比尔和考琳领养了一个小孩 他们一定会帮忙的
...Bill and Colleen. They adopted a kid. I'm sure they'd help you.
- 谢谢 那真是太好了   - 当然
- Thanks, that would be great.     - Sure.
老公 那是不是很棒
Hey, honey, wouldn't that be great?
好了… 记住我们刚刚说的
All right, all right. Remember what we talked about.
在公共场合 要有一定的规矩
When we're in a public place, there are certain rules.
我们不是这么说的
That's not what we talked about!
- 你好 法兰克   - 你好
- Hi, Frank.     - Hi.
- 很高兴看到你   - 我也很高兴看到你
- Good to see you.     - Good to see you too.
- 你好 法兰克   - 你好 最近如何？
- Hi, Frank.     - Hi. Hey, how you doing?
天啊 他们都这么大了 哪个是哪个啊
Oh, my goodness, they've all gotten so big. Which one is which again?
那个是小小法兰克
Oh, well, uh, uh, that's, uh, Frank Jr. Jr...
从那个小姐的皮包里扯出卫生棉条
...pulling the tampons out of the lady's purse.
钱德正往钱德的身上爬
And, uh, that's, uh, Chandler climbing on Chandler.
莱斯里正往他身上丢贝果
And, uh, that's Leslie throwing bagels at him.
"有领养三胞胎的意愿吗"？没有
"Willing to adopt triplets?" No.
我知道这么做是为了罗斯 而那是没关系的
Oh, can I just say, I know we're doing this for Ross and that's cool.
如果由我决定的话 我们的第一次约会 不会是这样的
But if it was up to me, this is not what we'd be doing on our first date.
那么 我们会做什么？
Well, what would we be doing?
我会带你度过一个浪漫的夜晚
I'd take you out for a romantic night.
一些香槟和大餐 然后在坐马车回家的路上抚摸你
Some champagne, fancy dinner, feel you up on the carriage ride home.
抚摸我？
Feel me up?
在 马车里
In a carriage.
- 你好 查莉   - 你好
- Hey, Charlie!     - Hi.
- 你好   - 你好
- Hi.     - Hey. Hmm.
那么…
So...
担心吗？ - 那是当然的
...dreading this?     - Oh, you bet.
- 嗯    - 嗯
- Mm.     - Mm-hm.
这是你带给罗斯的小礼物吗？
So did you, uh, bring a little something for Ross?
事实上 这是你留在我公寓的东西
Actually, uh, it's some stuff you left at my apartment.
喔 谢谢
Oh, well, thanks.
你随时可以把我的东西还给我
And you can just give me my stuff whenever you want.
好 我什么都没丢掉…
Yeah, I didn't throw any of that out. Heh, heh.
我就说我听到什么声音了
Ah, I thought I heard voices. What? Ha, ha.
你好  查莉
Hi, Charlie. Mwah.
- 你好   - 乔伊
- Hey, Joey. Ha.     - Hey.
你该向我介绍你的新女友
And, uh, oh, you're gonna have to introduce me to your new girlfriend.
我开玩笑的 我认识瑞秋 我认识
I'm just kidding. I know Rachel. I know... Uh...
进来 请进 进来
Come. Please come in. Come in.
我们带酒来了
Okay. Uh, well, we brought you some wine.
想得真周到
Oh. Ah. That is so thoughtful.
她是个值得留下的女人
She's a keeper. Ha.
- 你带了什么给我？ - 事实上 那是…
- And what did you bring me, huh?     - Uh, actually, that's, uh...
内裤 牙刷
Underwear, a toothbrush...
《范海伦合唱团》的CD
...and a Van Halen CD.
这些我都用得着
I can use all these things!
天啊 罗斯 你知道吗 你有点…
Gosh, Ross, you know, you seem a little, um...
什么？很好吗？因为我本来就很好
What? Fine? Because I am, huh?
你们呢…看吧
Aren't you? Aren't you? Aren't...? You see?
还有谁很好？
Who else is fine?
- 哈哈   - 快啊
- Ha, ha.     - Come on.
听着 试着放松点 来喝点什么
Listen. Why don't you, uh, try to relax. Maybe have a drink.
知道吗 那是个好主意
You know what, that is a very good idea.
我要去弄一壶玛格丽塔鸡尾酒
I'm gonna go make a pitcher of margaritas.
天啊
Oh, God.
真可爱
So adorable.
看他们睡着就像天使一样
Look at them, sleeping there like angels.
- 我也很珍惜这段时光   - 嗯
- Yeah, I really cherish these moments...     - Mm.
因为在你还来不及回首 他们就会醒过来
...because, uh, before you know it, they're gonna be awake again.
他们可能比较难控制
Well, they may be a handful...
可是他们真的很可爱    - 是
...but they're so cute.     - Yeah.
上次我看护他们时 他们做了很有意思的事
Oh, God, last time I babysat them, they did the funniest thing. Ha, ha.
我已经四年没睡觉了
I haven't slept in four years.
那是很长的时问
That's a long time.
你不知道这有多难 菲比
FRANK: You just don't know how hard it is, Phoebe.
他们的人数实在太多了
There's just so many of them.
两个我还能处理
You know, two I could handle.
两个就太好了 正好一手抱一个
Two's great. You just hold one in each hand.
可是第三个带着安全帽 向我冲过来时 我该怎么办？
What do I do when the third one runs at me with his bike helmet on?
我没有另一只手来保护我的要害
I got no more hands to protect my area.
他们有三个 菲比 三个
There's three of them, Phoebe. Three.
是 我知道 法兰克
Yeah, I know, Frank.
当他们从我的要害生出来时 我就数过了
I counted them when they were coming out of my area.
有时候我甚至想…
Sometimes, I think that, uh...
不…我不能说 太可怕了 不
Oh, no, no, no, I can't say it. It's too horrible. No.
什么？
What?
不 我不能
FRANK: No, no, I can't.
我的天 法兰克 你想离开吗？
Oh, my God, Frank. Are you thinking of leaving?
因为我生了这三胞胎 不是让你来抛弃的
Because I didn't have those triplets so you could run out on them.
不 我永远不会那么做 不 我只是想…
Oh, no, I would never do that. No. I just...
你知道吗 也许你可以带走一个
...was thinking that, you know, maybe you could take one.
什么？
What?
你不能把他们分开 这太可怕了 哪一个？
You can't separate them, that's terrible! Which one?
谢谢你们让我们来
Thank you so much for seeing us.
菲比说了有关你们很好的事情
Phoebe has told us great things about you guys.
请进 我们很愿意帮忙
Oh, please, we're happy to help.
我们领养的时候 也经历过同样的事情
We went through the same thing when we were adopting.
这客厅里可充满着故障的生产线 不是吗？
So a lot of malfunctioning wee-wees and hoo-hoos in this room, huh?
我是说 你家真是不错
I mean, you have a lovely home.
你们提供的任何资讯 我们都会很感激的
We appreciate anything you can tell us.
事实上 我想这会有帮助的
Well, actually, I think this might help.
这些大概…
It's pretty much...
就是你们需要的所有的资讯了   - 天啊
...all the information you need.     - Oh, my God.
所有的东西都分门别类 可以互相引用
Everything is broken into categories, then cross-referenced.
还依照后面的表格 以颜色进行标注
Then color-coded to correspond with the forms in the back.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我想我刚刚经历了一次小小的高潮
I think I just had a tiny orgasm.
我知道过程令人感到沮丧 不过一切都是值得的
I know the process is frustrating, but it's so worth it.
领养欧文是我们所经历过 最美好的事情
Adopting Owen was the best thing that ever happened to us.
太棒了 我能看看这资料吗？
That's great. Can I see the book?
你想叫我先去洗手 是不是？
You want me to wash my hands first, don't you?
拜托 这个那么的美丽 而且是白色的
Please. It's just so pretty and white.
洗手间在走廊尽头 向左走
Bathroom is down the hall to your left.
是我也会叫他去洗手
I would have told him to do it too.
我能领养你吗？
Can I adopt you?
- 你好 你一定是欧文了    - 对
- Hey, you must be Owen.     - Yeah.
我是钱德 我也当过童子军
I'm Chandler. Hey, I was in the Scouts too.
- 真的？ - 事实上我爸爸是童子军的训导员
- You were?     - In fact, my father was a den mother.
- 哈？ - 你知道怎么用指南针吗？
- Huh?     - You know how to use a compass?
我得过一枚徽章
I have a badge in it.
- 真的？真是太棒了    - 你想看吗
- You do? That's fantastic.     - You want to see it?
当然想 不过我得先回去跟你的父母聊聊
I'd love to, but I gotta get back to your parents.
他们在告诉我们 是怎么领养你的
They're telling us about how they adopted you.
什么？
What?
What?!
我是被领养的？
I'm adopted?
我什么都不知道
I got nothing.
第一批的玛格丽塔鸡尾酒不是很好
Well, that first batch of margaritas was not so great...
可是第二批实在不错
...but this second batch is good.
希望到下一批的时候 我们都能喝到一点
Well, maybe the next batch, we could all get some.
天啊 真是太好玩了 不是吗？
Oh, God, this is fun, isn't it?
知道吗 就我们四个人
You know, just the four of us.
就这么坐着
Just hanging. Ha.
老兄 你还好吧？
Dude, are you okay?
法士达面饼到底什么时候才会好？
And when are the fajitas gonna be ready?
我很好 我太好了
I'm fine, okay? I'm great.
我只是… 我只是为我们而骄傲
I'm just... I'm just proud of us.
一点都不会不自在 一点都不会紧张
You know? There's no weirdness, no tension.
一点都不清醒
No awareness.
我们是很棒的"四人帮" 应该一起再做些什么
We make a great foursome. We should do more stuff together.
我们去旅行吧
You know, oh, let's take a trip!
你觉得我们该去哪里？
Okay, where do you think we can go?
我的法士达面饼
My fajitas!
查莉 我想让你知道
Look, Charlie, I just want you to know...
罗斯还需要时间消化 我跟乔伊在一起
...Ross is just having a little trouble adjusting to the thought of Joey and me.
他通常不会这样喝的
He normally doesn't drink like this.
跟你说 这没什么 我爸爸就是个疯狂的酒鬼
Oh, you know what, this is nothing. My father is a raging alcoholic.
对不起 我让今晚尴尬了吗？
Oh, I'm sorry, have I made this evening uncomfortable?
法士达面饼 当心 盘子很烫 非常烫
Fajitas! Be careful! Very hot plate! Very hot!
罗斯 你怎么没戴手套？
Ross, you don't even have oven mitts on.
这明天可痛了
That is gonna hurt tomorrow.
这太疯狂了
Okay, well, this is crazy.
我们现在讨论要我带走一个孩子 不是认真的吧？
We can't seriously be talking about me taking one of your kids, can we?
不 当然不是
Oh, no, of course we're not.
- 太愚蠢了   - 我知道
- That's insane.     - I know.
爱丽丝不会同意的
Alice would never go for it.
她也累得要死 我想她可能会同意
She's pretty tired too. I think we could get her on board.
那我问你个假设性的问题
Well, just for argument's sake, you know, hypothetically...
你会愿意放弃哪一个？
...which one would you be willing to give up?
额
Huh.
小小法兰克？
Frank Jr. Jr?
那我的肩膀可以减轻负担
You'd be getting a really good one.
你选的这个真的很好 他真的很好笑
I mean, you know, he's really funny.
那天他说了个笑话
Like, the other day, he made up this joke:
什么东西是绿的并且说 "我是一只青蛙"？
What's green and says, "Hey, I'm a frog"?
一只会说话的青蛙
A talking frog.
不 你不能带他走 他太有意思了
Oh, no, you can't have him, he's too funny. Ha, ha.
好吧…没问题 那莱斯里呢？
Well, all right, that's fine. What about, um, Leslie?
不…莱斯里不行
Oh, no, no, not Leslie. No.
她是唯一一个 会打喝说出英文字母表的
She's the only one that knows how to burp the alphabet.
好吧 那就只剩下钱德了
All right, so that leaves Chandler.
不…你不能带走钱德 不…她是我的小天才
Oh, no, no, you can't have Chandler. No, no. She's my little genius.
我对她抱着很大期望
I got big hopes for her.
她会成为医生或是房地产经纪人
She's gonna be a doctor or a realtor.
法兰克 这样就没有小孩让我带了
Wow, Frank. Ha. I think we just ran out of kids.
我想你是对的
Oh, I think you're right.
菲比 我不认为我能放弃任何一个
Oh, wow. Phoebe, I don't think I can give one of them up.
虽然他们让我发疯 但是他们是我的宝贝
I mean, you know, they drive me crazy, but they're my babies.
很抱歉 法兰克 我没想到事情会这么糟
I'm sorry, Frank, I didn't realize things were so bad.
我可以帮你更多忙 在任何你需要的时候看顾他们
You know, I'll help out more. I can babysit anytime you want.
你叫我去 我就会去的
You name the day and I'll be there.
- 明天怎么样？ - 明天不行
- How about tomorrow?     - Well, that's not good.
但是我能把事情排开 我会到的
But I can move some stuff around and I'll be there.
你和爱丽丝去放一天假
You and Alice just take the whole day together.
你会为我们这么做？
Tsk. You'd do that for us?
你开玩笑吗？你以为姐姐是干什么用的？
Are you kidding? That's what sisters are for.
啊
Tsk. Oh.
看看他们
Oh, look at them.
我真爱你们
Oh. I love you so much.
天啊 别醒过来…
Oh, crap, don't wake up! Don't wake up!
- 比尔和考琳呢？ - 他们在厨房弄吃的
- Where are Bill and Colleen?     - Kitchen, getting something to eat.
- 你能想像他们有多好吗？ - 我们得走了
- Can you believe how nice they are?     - We have to leave.
为什么 你在洗手间做了什么？
Why? What did you do in the bathroom?
我还没去洗手间呢 我刚刚碰到了欧文
I didn't get to the bathroom. I bumped into Owen on the way.
他还不知道他是被领春的 有个小小的可能…
He didn't know he was adopted. There's a slight chance...
我可能告诉了他
...I may have told him.
天啊 我的皮包呢？不 里面的东西都能重新买
Oh, my God, where's my purse? No, I can replace everything in there.
- 拿着活页册 我们快走   - 你好
- Get that binder and let's go!     - Hi. Ha.
大家来吃点小点心
Some little snacks for everybody.
你们不必吃那些酸软糖 那些是欧文吃的
You don't have to eat the sour worms. Those are for Owen.
我一会儿去叫他
COLLEEN: I'll get him in a second.
顺带一提 你们该知道 我们还没告诉他他是领养的
Uh, by the way, you should know, we haven't told him he's adopted yet.
但是孩子的直觉是很敏锐的
But kids are so intuitive.
你不认为某种程度上他已经知道了
Don't you think, on some level, he already knows?
- 我是领养的？ - 看吧 直觉
- I'm adopted?     - See? Intuitive.
什么 你从哪听来的？
What? Where did you hear that?
他告诉我的
He told me.
他还给我50块钱叫我别说出来
And he paid me 50 dollars not to tell.
严格的说 你现在该把钱还给我了
Which, technically, now you should give back.
你告诉他 他是被领养的？
You told him he's adopted?
实在对不起 可是你们该写个警告立牌吧
I'm sorry. You should have a sign out there or something.
或者在人们进门的时候 悄悄告诉他们
Or at least whisper it to people when they come in the door.
欧文不知道自己被领养
"Owen doesn't know he's adopted...
也认为圣诞老人存在
...and he also thinks Santa is real."
他不是吗？
He isn't?
我们必须走了 亲爱的
We have to get out of here, baby.
各位 我要向…
Everyone, I would like to make a toast...
瑞秋和乔伊敬酒
...to Rachel and Joey.
还有爱情
And to love.
啊…爱情
Ah, love!
嗯
Mm.
L○VE 爱情
L-O-V-E. Love.
L代表生命
L is for "life."
没有爱情 生命又是什么？
And what is life without love?
我的天啊 我们需要回答吗？
Oh, my God, are we supposed to answer?
○代表…
O is for:
天啊
"Oh, wow!"
V代表着…
The V is for this...
事态快速的转变
...very surprising turn of events...
顺带一提 我完全应付得来
...which I am still fine with, by the way.
E…
E...
代表着…
is for how...
我发现这是一切是多么的正常
...extremely normal I find it...
你们两个…
...that you two...
走在一起
...are together.
有一天你们也许会结婚
And that one day you might get married...
拥有自己的孩子
...and have children of your own.
- 兄弟 你还好吧？ - 完全没问题
- Dude, are you okay?     - Totally.
罗斯 你看起来不太好
Ross, you don't seem okay.
对不起 一定是招待你们的压力太大了
I'm sorry, it must be the pressure of entertaining.
如果我们吃点布丁 应该会感觉好点
I think everyone would feel better if we had some flan.
等等 罗斯 我…我要走了
Wait, Ross. Ross, I, um... I have to take off.
- 不行   - 对不起
- No!     - I'm sorry.
我明天一早有课
I have an early class in the morning.
今天晚上真是愉快
But this has been lovely.
不是吗？你还以为乔伊会尴尬
Wasn't it? And you thought it would be awkward with Joey.
而且你不太喜欢瑞秋
And that you never really liked Rachel.
你神志不清了 我早上给你打电话 好吗？
You are on fire! I'll call you in the morning, okay?
- 好   - 好的
- Okay.     - All right.
天啊 瑞秋 罗斯刚才说的话简直太…
Rachel, what Ross just said, that's just...
没关系 女生通常不会喜欢我
Oh, that's okay. Girls tend not to like me.
好吧
Fine.
好吧 只需要准备 三人份的布丁了
Okay. I guess it's just flan for three.
嘿
Hey.
那还挺押韵的
Hey, that rhymes.
罗斯 我想我们也该走了
You know what, Ross, I think, uh, we're gonna take off too.
喔… 当然 天啊 我真蠢
Oh, oh. Heh. Of course. God, I'm so stupid.
你们现在是一对了
You guys are a couple now.
你们应该想独处
I mean, you probably just want to be alone.
- 不 我只是说时间很晚了…   - 没关系 真的
- No, it's just getting late...     - It's fine. It's totally fine.
我有很多玛格丽塔鸡尾酒 一切都很好
I've got plenty of margaritas. It's all good.
我根本不知道 那是为了什么而设定的
I don't even know what that's for.
你知道吗？
You know what?
我想我该留下来 确定他不会有事
I think I'm gonna stay here and make sure he's okay.
- 这可能是个好主意   - 明天早上见
- That's probably a good idea.     - I'll see you in the morning.
- 好   - 好
- Uh-huh. Okay.     - All right.
好 你知道吗 乔伊 我…
Yeah, you know, Joey, I...
我不认为他会接受我们两个在一起
I don't think he's ever gonna be okay with this.
- 看起来不太好 是吗？ - 嗯
- It doesn't look good, does it?     - Mm-mm.
早安
Morning.
- 给你   - 谢谢
- Here you go.     - Thanks.
- 你整个晚上都留在这里？ - 对
- Did you stay here all night?     - Yeah.
是你脱了我的裤子和鞋？
So you took off my pants and shoes?
不…
No. No, no.
是你听《芝加哥》 电影原声带的时候自己脱的
You actually did that when you were dancing to the Chicago soundtrack.
听着 罗斯
Ahem. Look, uh, Ross...
关于我和瑞秋 听着 你什么都不用担心
...about Rachel and I. Listen, you don't have to worry about that...
因为什么事都不会发生
...because nothing's gonna happen.
这是什么意思？
What do you mean?
我们从一开始就说好了
She and I said from the beginning...
如果你不接受的话 我们不会在一起的
...we weren't gonna do anything unless you were okay with it.
很明显的…
And clearly...
你在说什么？我很好
What are you talking about? I'm fine.
没关系 罗斯 我完全了解
It's okay, Ross. You know, I totally understand.
你当然不好 你们是…
Of course you're not fine. You're...
你们是罗斯和瑞秋
You're Ross and Rachel.
只是我们已经不是了
Yeah, except we're not.
我是说 我们没在一起已经有…
I mean, we haven't been a couple in, like...
六年了
...six years.
天啊 真的吗？
My God, is that right?
有这么久了？
Has it been that long?
我是这么听说的 是的
That's what I hear, yeah.
这太疯狂了 我是说 已经六年了…
This is crazy. I mean, six years...
只因为我 你们就不能在一起？
...and because of me, you guys aren't gonna be together?
我可以问你个问题吗？
Can I ask you something?
说真的…
Really...
你和瑞秋到底是怎么一回事？
...what is this thing with you and Rachel?
别闹了 你了解我 你知道的…
Come on, you know me. Ha, ha. You know...
乔伊
Joey.
我为她感到疯狂
I'm crazy about her.
她也这么想吗？
And she feels the same way?
我想是的
I think so.
好吧 那么…
Well, then...
也许是大家都向前看的时候到了
...maybe it's time we all moved on.
对 不过 罗斯 我是说 你并没有完全接受
Yeah, but, Ross, I mean, you're not okay with it, so...
不 但是我要接受
No, but I want to be.
嘿
And hey:
我会接受的
I will be.
况且  我还有查莉 对吧
Besides, I'm with Charlie, right?
天啊  我还跟查莉在一起吧？
Oh, my God, I'm still with Charlie, aren't I?
- 她没看见我跳舞吧？ - 没有…
- She didn't see the dance, did she?     - No, no, no.
没有 舞是为我而跳的
No, that was, uh... That was just for me.
你…
Hey, you, uh?
你确定吗？
You sure about this?
对 我确定
Yeah, I'm sure.
那…
And...
我们之间没问题吗？
...we're okay?
- 菲比   - 你好
- Hey, Pheebs.     - Hey.
我们想先提醒你一件事
Um, we just want to give you a heads up.
比尔和考琳讨厌我们
Bill and Colleen hate us.
欧文不知道自己是被领养的 摩妮卡却说出来了
Owen didn't know he's adopted and Monica told him.
什么？
What?
可是 他总有一天会知道的
Still, he had to find out sometime.
如果有人告诉三胞胎 他们是你生的又如何？
How would you like it if someone told the triplets that you gave birth to them?
我要去告诉艾玛说她是个意外
I'm gonna go tell Emma she was an accident.